"You love pottery? I love pottery."
(Leonard:)You know, there's a pause.
We both know what's happening.
(Leonard:)We kiss. It's a little tentative at first.
But I realize, she's kissing me back,
she's biting my lower lip.
(Leonard:)She wants me.
This thing is going the distance.
We're gonna have sex.
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
(Sheldon:)Is the sex starting now?
(Leonard:)I'm having a panic attack.
(Sheldon:)Oh, okay. Well, then, calm down.
(Sheldon:)If I could,
I wouldn't be having an attack.
(Leonard:)- That's why they call it a panic attack.
- All right.
Would you just sit down?
- Yeah, sit down. Now close your eyes.
- Why?
- Just do it.
- Okay.
(Sheldon:)Now, try to increase
your alpha-wave activity.
- What?
- It's a biofeedback technique.
(Sheldon:)It's relaxation
through brainwave manipulation.
I read it
in the Journal of American Neuroscience.
It was sparsely sourced,
but I think the science is valid.
(Sheldon:)I probably have it here somewhere.
Who am I kidding?
I can't go through with this.
(Leonard:)- You need to call her and cancel.
- Me?
(Leonard:)- Yes.
- What should I tell her?